女妖镇警署
警长在吗
Is the sheriff in?
洛特斯警长正在开会  请问有什么事吗
Sheriff Lotus is in a meeting. Can I help you?
有他需要知道的消息
I have information he needs to hear.
请问有事吗  女士
Can I help you, ma'am?
他想让你知道他不会停手
He wants you to know he won't stop.
杀那些女孩只是个开始
Taking those girls was just the beginning.
-这是怎么回事  -他想让你看到
- What is this? - He wants you to see.
让你们都看到
You will all see.
你他妈在干嘛
What the hell are you doing?
不要  不要
Don't! No!
不要
Don't do it!
黑吃黑
第四季
第六集
加尔文
Calvin.
你去哪里了
Where have you been?
你这是怎么了
What happened to you?
那是血吗
Is that blood?
-加尔文  加...  -别出声
- Calvin. Cal-- - Quiet.
走...求你  停下
Get-- stop, please. Stop.
你他妈怎么回事
What the fuck is wrong with you?
没事  你不要这么粗鲁
Nothing, just not so rough.
-求你了  -天啊
- Please. - Jesus.
等一下  你在跟别人上床吗
Wait a second. Are you screwing somebody else?
什么  当然没有
What? No. Of course not.
我们好几个月没上床了  到底怎么了
We haven't fucked in months. What is it?
你...
You just--
吓到我了
you scared me.
你吓到我了
You scared me.
到底怎么了  发生什么事了
What happened? What's going on?
你到底怎么了
What happened to you?
不要  加尔文
No, Calvin.
加尔文  加尔文
Calvin. Calvin.
你可以洗了
Shower's all yours.
来一管吧
Help yourself.
我不吸
Not really my thing.
我是从做卧底开始的
You know, I started out in undercover.
漂亮的白人小妞
Pretty white chicks have to
要证明自己总得多牺牲一点
go a little bit further to prove themselves.
所以要么跟他们上床
So it was either fuck 'em
要么吸他们的东西
or smoke their shit.
有时候两者都有
Sometimes it was both.
你不用跟我解释
You don't have to explain yourself to me.
我一直想戒掉的
I've been meaning to kick it.
但是成天泡在这堆破事里
But when you spend your days up to your neck in this shit,
有时我需要放松一下
sometimes I got to get out of my own head.
我需要担心你吗
Do I need to worry about you?
不
No.
如果你担心那我谢谢你
Might be nice if you did.
朋友  你有点怕跟人亲密啊
Wow, you, my friend, have some intimacy issues.
谢谢你让我在这里过夜
Thanks for letting me crash.
本来可以一起睡床上的
Could have shared the bed.
随口说说
Just saying.
你他妈是谁
Who the fuck are you?
玛吉
Maggie.
-科特  -怎么了
- Kurt. - What's wrong?
-是...  -你想坐下吗
- It-- it's-- - You want to sit for a second?
不  我不想坐
No, I don't want to sit.
海伦  你能带汉克
Helen, you think you could get Hank here
去楼上拿零食吃吗
one of those snacks that you keep upstairs?
好的  汉克
Sure. Hi, Hank.
跟我来好吗
Want to come with me?
谢谢
Thank you.
过来
Come here.
怎么了  他伤害你了吗
What happened? Did he hurt you?
那个混蛋
That motherfucker.
我离开那里了  那房子里一秒钟都待不下去
I left. I couldn't be in that house another second.
-他让你走了  -他不知道
- He let you leave? - He doesn't know.
我就带着汉克
I just grabbed Hank
打包了东西  然后
and packed things and...
我甚至都不知道要去哪里  科特
I don't even know where I'm going, Kurt.
-去跟我一起住  -不行
- You'll stay with me. - I can't.
他肯定首先就去那里找我们
That's the first place he's gonna come look.
除非我先找到他
Not if I find him first.
不
No.
不  我得为汉克考虑
No, I have to think about Hank.
科特
Kurt,
我觉得他杀了我父亲
I think he killed my father.
兰德尔死了
Randall's dead?
我不知道  他们一起走了  然后
I don't know. They left together and then--
然后加尔文浑身是血
and then Calvin-- and he was covered in blood.
然后他...
And-- and then he--
他让人很害怕
it was-- he was terrifying.
好了  别说了
Okay. Shh.
没事了
It's okay.
那是我妈的毛衣
That's my mother's sweater.
是的
It is.
她从没穿过
She never wears it.
-你穿着挺好看  -我穿什么都好看
- It looks good on you. - Most things do.
你最好在你妈回来前把那边的玻璃打扫干净
You best clean that glass up before your mother gets home.
知道了  我马上打扫
Yeah, I'll get right on that.
你是怎么被卷进这堆破事里的
So how do you fit into this whole shit show?
你爸妈和我
Your mother and your father and I
很久前就认识
go way back.
是吗  哪个爸
Yeah? Which father?
遗传你那副伶牙俐齿的
The one that gave you that smart mouth.
知道了
Got it.
那她对你来说是卡莉还是安娜
So is she Carrie or Ana to you?
卡莉是我造出来的
There weren't no Carrie before I invented her.
我也想重新以新的身份开始
Well, I could use a shiny new life myself.
你可以帮我吗  你欠我的
You want to hook me up? I figure you owe me.
你真是个不良少年
Ain't you the fucked-up little delinquent?
我只是想随机应变活下去
Hey, I'm just trying to play the shitty hand I was dealt.
姑娘  你应对的是
Girl, what you were dealt
会为了你杀人或为你而死的父母
were two parents who would kill or die for you.
这比大部分人要应对的多很多
That's a hell of a lot more than most people got.
蒂法
Deva.
你怎么来了
What are you doing here?
我也想你  妈
Missed you, too, Mom.
我只是看到你很惊喜
I'm just surprised to see you.
你又把门锁换了
You changed the locks on the door again.
抱歉  我该告诉你的
Sorry, I should have told you.
-你奶奶知道你来这里吗  -我给她留了字条
- Does Grandma know you're here? - I left her a note.
反正他们也不会想我
I really don't think they'll miss me.
-蒂法  -我不回去了  妈
- Deva. - I'm not going back, Mom.
那里没有网络  还臭气熏天
There's no Wi-Fi and it smells like ass there.
-亲爱的  如果法庭发现  -不会的
- Honey, if the court finds out-- - They won't.
-反正我可以保守秘密  -你不要插手
- I know I can keep a secret. - You stay out of this.
这么说你可能会接受  因为你真没有选择余地
If it makes it any easier, you really don't have a choice.
为什么不去直接逮捕加尔文
All right, so why don't we just arrest Calvin?
她绝不会作证指控他
She'll never testify against him.
她吓坏了
She's terrified.
她认为加尔文杀了她父亲
She thinks Calvin killed her father.
加尔文知道吗
Does Calvin know?
-知道什么  -你们俩的事
- Does Calvin know what? - About you two.
-不知道  -你确定吗
- No. - You sure?
-确定  -你以为我看不出来
- Yeah. - 'Cause you didn't think I could tell
可我只用了十秒就看出来了
and it took me all of about 10 seconds to see it.
虽然我比一般警察聪明
Now, granted, I'm a smarter than average cop
-但他可是个仇恨一切的混蛋  -加尔文不知道
- and he's a hatemongering asshole. - Calvin doesn't know.
他们可以去我那里
They can stay at my place.
-真的吗  -真的
- Really? - Yeah.
直到你想到办法扳倒你兄弟
Just until you find a way to take your brother down.
-谢谢  -不客气
- Thank you. - You're welcome.
顺便  你没事吧
Hey, you okay, by the way?
今天早上  自焚的事
This morning, the burning.
肯定让你回忆起不好的了吧
Must have hit pretty close to home, huh?
我没事
Yeah, I'm fine.
我能一直闻到那股味
Can't get that smell out of my head.
需要时间
It takes a while.
干洗店
-请问有什么可以帮你吗  -我觉得你帮不了
- Can I help you? - I highly doubt it.
你不能去后面
You can't go back there.
-你不能去后面  -我知道
- You can't go back there. - I know.
这是肿胀  会消下去...
That's the swelling, babe. They'll soften up--
-天啊  -你不能来这里
- Sweet Jesus. - Hey, hey, you can't be in here.
可我就来了  联调局
And yet I am. FBI.
亲爱的  离开这里
Honey, get out of here.
大卫· 奎克医生
Dr. David Quick.
我一直在找你
I have been looking for you.
你好啊  医生
What's up, Doc?
还是坐下吧
Why don't you take a seat?
要再来一遍吗
Should we try that again?
被吊销行医执照后
Performing breast augmentation
还给人做隆胸手术
after being stripped of your medical license,
这可是重罪
now, that's a felony.
我们这里不做手术
We don't perform any procedures here.
蒂芙尼是我的朋友
Tiffany is a friend of mine.
她让我帮她看看她的隆胸效果而已
She asked me to look at her boob job, that's all.
-那你为什么跑  -我不喜欢警察
- Mm, so why'd you run? - I don't like cops.
你不能进去  伙计
Hey, you can't go in there, buddy.
你有搜查令吗
You got a warrant?
我不需要搜查令
I don't need one.
我又不是警察
I'm not a cop.
听着  我们可以来那一套
Yeah, look, we can go down that road,
但最后会变得复杂又无聊  你也还是会输
but it's tangled and boring and in the end, you'll still lose.
或者你可以回答我几个问题
Or you can answer a few questions
我就当我们没见过面
and I'll forget we ever met.
看这里
Over here.
好
Okay.
你想知道什么
What do you want to know?
-身体改造  -怎么了
- Body modifications. - What about it?
-你做吗  -偶尔做  这块儿正在发展
- You do it? - Now and then. It's a growing field.
所以你肯定做一些很变态的咯
So you must do some pretty fucked-up shit.
我拒绝做的那些更变态
Not as fucked up as the shit I turn down.
大家想要的东西  说了你都不会信
You wouldn't believe the kind of things people want.
天啊  老兄
Hey, Jesus, man!
那玩意儿很贵
Shit's expensive.
我在找一个做了角植入的人
I'm looking for a guy with horn implants.
-你做过那种手术吗  -做过
- You ever do anything like that? - Yeah.
那给我看看档案  医生
Well, then whip out your files, Doc.
那种手术我们不留档案
We don't keep files on that kind of stuff.
我想有意向做魔角植入的人并不多
I can't imagine devil horns is a common request.
比你想的要多
They're more common than you think.
这可是撒旦的国度
It's Satan's country out here.
没错  但还是很特别
Yeah, but still, it's pretty unique,
你也没遇到几例
even for a guy like you.
你最后一次是给谁做的
Who was the last guy you did?
我肯定你还有点印象
I'm sure you remember something.
想要做这手术的人
The kind of people who want this shit,
他们根本不是普通公民
they're not exactly model citizens.
我先收现金  不会问他们的姓名
I take cash in advance. I don't even ask their names.
你可真方便
How convenient for you.
你们太过分了
This is bullshit.
我要打给我的律师
I'm gonna call my lawyer.
走吧
Let's go.
他什么都不知道
He doesn't know anything.
这次谈话我很不满意  奎克医生
This has not been a satisfying conversation for me, Dr. Quick.
我要是你  就会给我打电话
If I were you, I'd call me.
多谢
Thank you.
我还没对那家伙下手呢
I barely started working that guy.
他不会说的
He wasn't gonna talk.
这或许有用
This might help.
这是他桌上的
That was on his desk.
朋友你可真有几手
You, my friend, have some serious skills.
他一直盯着你  我也是
He was watching you the whole time, so was I.
-你怎么拿到的  -要的就是这个效果
- How'd you do it? - That's the trick, isn't it?
我以为自己算见过世面的了
Just when I thought I'd seen it all.
没想到自卑对反社会的人影响这么大
Wow, amazing what low self-esteem can do to a sociopath.
女妖镇市政厅
我一直在找你
I've been trying to reach you.
我一直很忙
I've been busy.
咱们有麻烦了吗  克鲁兹副警长
We have a problem, Deputy Cruz?
没有  但说到麻烦
Not at all. But speaking of problems,
记得你让我调查的那事吗
remember that matter you asked me to look into?
-记得  -我调查了
- Yeah. - I looked into it.
你找到他了
You found him?
没  我找到她了
No, I found her.
此审判开始前五天
Exhibit number four was also turned in
四号证物已经上交给了听证官
to our hearing officer five days before this trial began.
如果法庭允许  你们会看到照片上
Now, if it pleases the court, you'll note that the photograph
是一扇后侧门破裂后的残余物
shows the remnants of a crushed back side door.
-照片是五个月前... -霍普韦尔夫人
- This photograph was taken at the scene... - Mrs. Hopewell.
在十字路口肇事逃逸现场拍摄的
of a hit-and-run five months back at the intersection...
最近几天我常在法院附近看到你
I'm seeing you around the courthouse quite often these days.
开始对法律感兴趣了
Taking an interest in the law?
可以那么说
You could say that.
我一直没机会对你丈夫去世
You know, I never really had the chance
表达我的哀悼之情
to offer my condolences for the loss of your husband.
你恨戈登
You hated Gordon.
不  我不恨他
No, didn't hate him.
我很尊敬他
I respected him.
那从不是个人恩怨
I never took it personally.
我希望他也是这么想
I'd like to think he didn't either.
他不是
He did.
不管怎样  我对此表示遗憾
Well, either way, I was very sorry to hear about it.
你外甥女的事我也很遗憾
I'm sorry about your niece.
我们都失去了很多
We both suffered a great loss.
有时那种损失
You know, sometimes a loss like that
会影响人的判断力
clouds the judgment.
令我们冲动行事
Makes us do things impulsively.
会为之后悔的事
Things we might regret.
你懂我什么意思吗
Do you know what I mean?
不太懂
No, not really.
不懂  我会小心的
No? Well, I'd watch out for it.
你还有那么多能失去的
You still have so much to lose.
我们都一样
I guess we all do.
那咱们都该更加小心
I suppose we both should be more careful.
记得我吗  小靓仔
Remember me, sunshine?
记得  不懂该何时闭嘴不问的贱货
Yeah, the bitch who didn't know when to stop asking questions.
你还记得  受宠若惊
Ah, you remembered. I'm so flattered.
我也是戴警徽的贱货
I'm also the bitch with the badge.
那天我没提到这点吗
Did I not mention that the other day?
-我不想惹麻烦  好吗  -这才对嘛
- I don't want any trouble, all right? - Now that's the spirit.
我们在找有魔角的家伙
We're looking for a guy with devil horns.
你在这见过吗
You got people like that in here?
见过  是身体改造
Yeah, body mods.
好  这家伙在屠杀姑娘
Right, well, this guy is killing girls.
翻翻这些照片  看能认出谁
Why don't you scroll through here, see if you recognize anyone?
来这里的所谓的撒旦教徒
Look, most of the so-called Satanists
大部分都是游客
that come in here are tourists.
他们这些混蛋没有看上去那么
They're assholes looking to be more edgier
嚣张  霸道
and bad-ass than they really are.
这家伙是个例外
With the exception of this guy.
这是谁
Who's this?
博德  德克兰·博德
That's Bode. Declan Bode.
他是祭祀的忠实拥护者
He's a hardcore ritualist.
-他常来这里吗  -以前有段时间常来
- Does he come here often? - Nah, used to a while back.
探别人虚实  也许在找信徒  不清楚
Feeling people out. Maybe looking for followers. I don't know.
没人喜欢他  因为他有点太狂热了
Nobody took to the guy 'cause he was a little too committed.
所以你是说这家伙太变态了
So you're talking about a guy who was so twisted,
都吓坏了其它恶魔主义崇拜者吗  懂了
he creeped out other Satanists? Got it.
-在哪能找到他  -我他妈怎么知道
- Where do we find him? - Fuck if I know.
-你知道他名字  -我也只能说这么多  条子
- You knew his name. - Yeah, and that's all I'm telling you, cop.
-他妈上哪找他  -我他妈也不知道
- Where do we fucking find him? - I don't fucking know, man.
-在哪儿  -我真不知道
- Where? - I don't fucking know.
那个混蛋认为被恶魔附身了
The fucking guy thinks the Devil works through him, all right?
有一晚那个变态来这里
One night the freak comes in here,
开始滔滔不绝讲述他如何与路西法交流
starts spouting off about how he's talking to Lucifer.
我说他在胡说
I tell him he's full of shit.
那家伙从我手中夺过水果刀
Guy takes the paring knife out of my hand,
开始把他的指甲一个个剥下来
starts peeling back his fingernails one by one,
边剥边笑
smiling the whole time.
然后点了杯喝的  这他妈是人干的事吗
Then he orders a drink. Who the fuck does that?
我们应该见见这家伙
Someone we should meet.
瞧见没  相互帮助  大家开心
See? When we're helping, we're happy.
是吗  有点意思
Yeah? Well, that's interesting.
好的
Okay.
好的  谢谢  我会再打给你
All right, thanks. I'll call you back.
我们要找的德克兰·博德没什么踪迹可寻
Our boy Declan Bode doesn't have much of a footprint.
没有地址  没有亲戚
No known address. No relatives.
但他确实有前科
But he does have a prior.
十五年前  他在临近的县被判强奸罪
He was convicted of statutory rape 15 years ago next county over.
-受害人的名字被封存了  -我们可以查看吗
- Girl's name is sealed. - Can we get it unsealed?
可以  但我需要法庭命令
Yes, but I will need a court order,
明天才可以拿到
which won't happen until tomorrow.
老天啊
Oh, Jesus Christ.
你有认识比较熟的法官吗
Don't you have any judges you can wake up?
你可能想不到
It might surprise you to learn
我在联邦法官那里不怎么受欢迎
I'm not very popular among the federal judges.
好吧  那我们现在做什么
All right, so what do we do now?
我们等
Now we wait.
就这么等着
Just wait?
是的
Yeah.
好极了
Great.
你不习惯停下来  对吗
You're not built for downtime, are you?
你的行动方式  你的步幅
The way you move, the way you pace,
你想直接穿过每堵墙
the way you want to push through every wall
甚至都不看有没有门或者有没有钥匙
without even looking for the door or the key to that door.
你想说什么
You have a point?
这种性情可不像是
That's not the temperament of a man
一路升上来的执法人员该有的
who worked his way up through law enforcement.
非要逼我说的话
Put my feet to the fire,
你比起警察你更像罪犯
I'd say you're more criminal than cop.
你不了解我
You don't know me.
我知道你坐不住
I know you can't sit still.
我猜你曾经被迫坐视不管
I'm guessing you were once made to for a very long time
你并不喜欢
and you didn't like it.
你每进入一个房间都会检查角落
You check the corners every time you enter a room.
那不是警察的训练  那是求生本能
That's not police training. That's survival.
你对我的态度很复杂
Your demeanor towards me is complicated.
你很难跟人对视
You have trouble making eye contact.
不是因为缺乏自信
It's not lack of confidence.
你有秘密
You've got a secret.
或者很多秘密
Or secrets.
也许只是因为我不喜欢你
Maybe I just don't like you.
但你喜欢我
But you do.
不是吗
Don't you?
你以为你了解我
You think you know me?
让我告诉你吧  你完全不了解我
Let me tell you something. You have no fucking idea.
对  我是一直都检查每个角落
Yeah, I check the corners because for as long as I can remember,
因为总会有人在那里
there's always been someone waiting there
等着来偷袭我
to get the jump on me.
我不能坐视不理  因为我每次放手不管
And I don't stay still 'cause every time I do,
跟我关系好的人就会死
someone close to me fucking dies.
抱歉
I'm sorry.
不用道歉
No, you're not.
是的  我不用
No, I'm not.
没事
It's nothing.
怎么了
What is it?
抱歉
I'm sorry.
连环杀手还没被抓到...
There is a serial killer out there...
-很吓人  -我知道  宝贝
- It's terrifying. - I know, baby. I know.
-我去巡逻  -应该到我了
- I'll take patrol. - It's my shift.
不  我要滥用一下职权逃离这个"动物园"
No, I'm pulling rank. I've got to get out of this zoo.
好吧
Okay.
女巫镇警署
谁在那儿
Someone there?
妈的
Shit.
这么晚还加班呢
Burning the midnight oil, I see.
这里不是谈生意的地方  加尔文
This is not the place to talk business, Calvin.
没事  因为我们没什么生意可谈了
That's fine because we no longer have any business to discuss.
兄弟会不再为你效力了
The Brotherhood no longer works for you.
-是这样吗  -是的  就是这样
- Is that so? - Yes, that is so.
那真是令人遗憾
Well, that's unfortunate.
我可不这么认为
Not from where I'm sitting.
我不禁想知道沃茨怎么看这件事
I can't help but wonder what Watts will think about this.
不如我们问问来他吧
Well, why don't we ask him?
兰道尔  你怎么看
What do you think, Randall?
沃茨怎么不吱声呢
Seems the cat got Watts's tongue.
这么做挺有种的
That's a bold choice.
是啊
Yeah.
我以为你会喜欢
I thought you'd like that.
我们以后这么办
So here's how it's gonna work.
你的一切都归我们
Everything that's yours is now ours.
仓库  货物  买家
Warehouses, shipments, buyers,
我他妈全部都要
I fucking want all of it.
你要么乖乖退出  要么我们头破血流
You can go quietly or you can go bloody,
但总之你必须滚蛋
but either way you are gone.
人头给你留着当纪念吧
You can keep the head as a souvenir.
我在电视上看见你了
I saw you on TV.
我不是自愿的
I didn't ask for this.
他选中了我
He chose me.
你明白吗
Do you understand?
他选中了我
He chose me.
你阻止不了我
You can't stop me.
我的使命
I've been delivered
就是喂饱野兽
to feed the beast.
我变得与众不同  超越凡人
I've become something different, something more.
而你  你只是一只爬虫
And you, you're a bug.
在他的权威面前如此卑微
A tiny, worthless insect in the face of his power.
操你妈
Fuck you.
把眼睛闭上  警察
Close your eyes, cop.
闭上眼睛
Close your eyes.
珍惜这眼前的黑暗
Cherish the darkness,
很快你就会亲眼见证他的计划
for soon you will bear witness to his plan.
直到那时
And only then
我才会取你可怜的小命
will I take your miserable little life.
柯特  他们在哪
Where are they, Kurt?
滚出我家
Get the fuck off my property.
我老婆呢
Where's my wife?!
她在安全的地方
She's somewhere safe.
等她准备好了  会打给你的
She'll call you when she's ready.
你在搅和我的家人  柯特
You are fucking with my family, Kurt.
我妻子和我儿子
My wife, my son.
你知道我他妈会把你怎么样吗
Do you have any idea what I will fucking do to you for that?
沃茨呢
Where's Watts?
沃茨死了
Watts is dead.
玛吉在哪
Where's Maggie?
她不想见你
She doesn't want to see you.
操你妈  你没资格告诉我
Fuck you. You don't get to fucking tell me that.
我就说了  现在我要进屋了
I just did. I'm going into my house.
两分钟后  如果你还在这儿
In two minutes, if you're still here,
我就会出来
I'll come back out.
信我  我要是出来  后果很严重
Trust me, you don't want me to come back out.
柯特
Kurt.
你还记得爸曾经带我们
Do you remember Dad used to take us
去范德格里夫特看斗狗吗
to the dogfights over in Vandergrift?
记得
Yeah.
我记得有一次我问他
I remember I once asked him...
如果比赛平局了怎么办
if the matches ever ended in a tie.
他嘲笑我
And he laughed at me
然后对我说
and he said,
"两犬相争  必有一死"
"There's only ever one way that a dogfight ends."
你还记得吗
You remember that?
记得
Yeah, I remember.
必有一死  柯特
There's only one way, Kurt.
我知道
I know.
蒂法
Deva!
-你受伤了吗  -没有
- Are you hurt? - No.
过来  过来
Come on. Come on.
出去  到屋顶上去
Get out there. Get on the roof.
-什么  -快
- What? - Go, go, go!
拿着  保险栓打开了
Here, take this. Safety's off.
两只手握住  瞄准后射击
Two hands. Point and squeeze.
找个地方躲好  等着  注意安全
Find a place to hide, wait. You stay safe.
走  快
Go. Now!
不
No.
我真是受够了
I am sick and tired...
为了保住小命  挣扎求生
of fighting for my motherfucking life.
该死
Damn.
蒂法呢
Where's Deva?
蒂法  你受伤了吗
Deva. Are you hurt?
给我
Give me this.
对不起
I'm sorry.
蒂法
Deva.
别着急  慢点说
Slow down. Slow down.
你没事吧  受伤了吗
You okay? You hurt?
好的
Okay.
我只想回家
I just want to go home.
我知道
I know.
问题是  我不知道家在哪儿
The thing is, I don't know where that is.
过来
Come here.
安德伍德  告诉我你有所发现
Underwood, tell me you have something.
法官解封了卷宗
The judge unsealed the file.
那起强奸案的受害者是金姆·牛顿
The victim on that statutory rape is a Kim Newton.
她还住在那一带
She still lives in the area.
-有地址吗  -刚发邮件给你了
- You got an address? - Just emailed it to you.
你最棒了  欠你个人情
You're the best. I owe you.
你欠我太多了
You owe me many.
这该死的镇子到底怎么了
What is it with this fucking town?
就没有一周
Can't we go one week
什么军队不朝我们开枪吗
without some motherfucking army shooting at us?
看上去你们应对得还行
Seems like you handled it fine.
那是因为这已经成为了一个他妈的习惯
That's because it's already become a motherfucking habit.
谢谢你
Thank you.
宝贝儿  外面有另一个世界
Baby, there's a whole world out there.
都这么跟我说的
So they tell me.
怎么回事
What the fuck happened here?
普罗克托
Proctor.
你去招惹他干什么
What are you doing messing with him?
你逗我吗
Are you kidding me?
你没资格每隔几年
You don't get to walk into my life
就走进我的生活  还质问我
every few years and question me.
蒂法可能被杀死的
Hey, hey, Deva could have been fucking killed.
滚
Get out of here.
-拜托  安娜  -给我滚
- Come on, Ana. - Get the fuck out of here!
你以为你是谁有资格跟我说这些
Who the fuck do you think you are saying that shit to me?
你以为我不知道可能会发生什么吗
Do you think I don't know what could have happened there?
你以为我不知道
You think I don't know what--
别说了
Stop.
没事了
It's okay.
你好  有何贵干
Hello. Can I help you?
金姆·牛顿吗
Kim Newton?
是的
Yes.
是我父母报的警
My parents were the ones that called the police.
我那时15岁
I was 15,
德克兰  他25岁
Declan, he was 25.
我以前很文静
I was a quiet girl.
在学校没有很多朋友
You know, I didn't have many friends in school.
总是坐在后排
Always the kid in the back row.
没人注意我
Nobody really paid any attention to me.
然后我遇到了德克兰
And then I met Declan.
他说我很美  我能看出他是真心的
He told me I was beautiful and I could tell he meant it.
我以前连吻都没接过
I had never even been kissed before
而这个帅气的年长男人
and here was this handsome older guy
疯狂地爱上了我
falling head over heels in love with me.
现在我知道是我当时太年轻  没判断力
And I understand now that I was young and impressionable
他对我耍了手腕儿  但  你懂的
and he manipulated me, but, you know...
我仍然觉得他爱过我
I still think he loved me
我知道我爱过他
and I know I loved him.
那么发生什么了
So what happened?
我爸发现了
My dad found out.
他想拿着卸胎棒去找德克兰
He wanted to go after Declan with a tire iron,
但我妈说服了他去报警而不是用武力
but my mother convinced him to call the police instead.
我哭了好多天
Oh, I cried for days.
性关系呢
And the sex?
有没有很变态
Was it perverse in any way?
很激烈  但不变态
It was intense, but, no,
我不觉得那是变态
I wouldn't say it was perverse.
德克兰遇到麻烦了吗
Is Declan in some kind of trouble?
他是犯罪嫌疑人
He's a person of interest.
你上次联系他是什么时候
When was the last time you spoke to him?
他被捕的那晚
The night he was arrested.
在那之后  我就再没见过他
After that, I never saw him again.
你家真漂亮
It's a nice piece of property you have.
谢谢
Oh, thanks.
我父母留给我的
My parents left it to me.
如果你有想到什么
Well, if you think of anything else,
就联系我
give me a call.
-谢谢你的配合  -好的
- Thanks for your time. - Yeah.
我是维罗妮卡
Hey, it's Veronica.
今早你不辞而别
You disappeared on me this morning.
总之  我找到了强奸案的受害者
But, anyway, I tracked down our statutory rape victim.
她说的话没有可疑
She said all the right things,
但直觉告诉我  她在说谎
but my bullshit meter is ringing.
不管怎样  我要回酒店了
Anyway, I'm going back to the hotel,
打给我  我再跟你说
so call me and I'll fill you in on my--
糟了
Oh, shit.
听说你在找我
I heard you were looking for me.